[music]
[音乐]
Hello and welcome to section 7
您好，欢迎来到第7节
of lesson 3. This is really just the conclusion
第3课的内容
of the entire course where I want to recap on
我想回顾的整个课程
all the different aspects that we've looked at over the 3
我们研究了3个方面的所有不同方面
lessons that we've been doing. Firstly
我们一直在做的课程。首先
let's just recap on Lambda expressions. The important thing about Lambda expressions
让我们回顾一下Lambda表达式。关于Lambda表达式的重要事项
is that it gives us a simple way now
是它现在给我们一种简单的方法
to define behavior. Behavior that we can assign to a variable,
定义行为。我们可以分配给变量的行为，
behavior that we can pass as a parameter. Rather than using
我们可以作为参数传递的行为。而不是使用
these anonymous inner classes that we had before with
这些我们以前使用过的匿名内部类
rather complex syntax it's very simple, very clean way
相当复杂的语法，非常简单，非常简洁
of allowing us to pass behavior as a parameter.
允许我们将行为作为参数传递。
Where you can use a Lambda expression
在哪里可以使用Lambda表达式
is anywhere where the type of the object that you're going to use
在您将要使用的对象类型的任何地方
whether it's a parameter or a variable you're assigning to is a functional interface.
您要分配给它的参数还是变量都是函数式接口。
Remember a functional interface is one that has
请记住，函数式接口是具有
only one abstract method, but that doesn't necessarily mean
只是一种抽象方法，但这并不一定意味着
now in JDK 8 that it only has one method in the interface.
现在在JDK 8中，它在接口中只有一种方法。
What the Lambda expression does
Lambda表达式的作用
is provide an implementation of that abstract method.
提供了该抽象方法的实现。
You can think of an Lambda expression like a method, but remember it's not associated
您可以将Lambda表达式视为一种方法，但是请记住它没有关联
with a class therefore it's an anonymous function.
因此，它是一个匿名函数。
In terms of the stream API
就流API而言
what this gives us is a way of having a pipeline of operations
这给我们带来了一种运作流程的方式
so that we can process collections of data.
这样我们就可以处理数据收集。
Number of elements of data can be processed this way.
数据元素的数量可以用这种方式处理。
We can acquire sources
我们可以获取资源
for a stream from various different places. The collections API
从不同的地方流。集合API
is one that has a number of ways of doing that, but there are other places
有很多方法可以做到这一点，但是还有其他地方
in the standard classes where you can get streams from.
在可以从中获取流的标准类中。
In terms of files, in terms of directories, zip files and so on.
在文件方面，在目录，zip文件等方面。
The important thing about streams is that they can be processed
关于流的重要一点是可以对其进行处理
sequentially or in parallel and, for the majority of the time,
顺序或并行，并且在大多数情况下，
the way that they're processed, whether it's sequential or parallel
处理的方式，无论是顺序的还是并行的
won't affect the outcome and the code to use is exactly the same regardless of
不会影响结果，并且无论使用什么代码都完全相同
how it's being processed.
处理方式。
In terms of the structure of the
在结构上
stream you have a source then potentially intermediate operations
流您有一个源，然后可能是中间操作
and some form a terminal operation. How the
还有一些形成终端操作。如何
intermediate operation and how the terminal operation
中间操作以及终端操作方式
actually works is often defined using Lambda expressions.
实际上有效的方法通常是使用Lambda表达式定义的。
That's the reason Lambda expressions were introduced into JDK 8
这就是Lambda表达式引入JDK 8的原因
so that we could build the stream API in a simple way. Terminal operations,
这样我们就可以以简单的方式构建流API。终端操作
because we don't know whether they will actually return something that is
因为我们不知道他们是否会真正返回
value return an optional and the
值返回可选值，并且
optional class now allows us to avoid a lot of the problems we had in the past
可选类现在使我们能够避免过去遇到的许多问题
with using a null reference and potentially having
使用空引用并可能具有
a NullPointerException. Putting all these things together
NullPointerException。将所有这些东西放在一起
we now have a functional style of programming
我们现在有了一种编程的函数式风格
available to us in Java. One of the really important things as a Java
用Java提供给我们。作为Java真正重要的事情之一
programmer
程序员
when you approach using Lambda expressions and streams
当您使用Lambda表达式和流时
is that you do need to think differently. What you've got to do
是你确实需要换个角度思考。你要做的
is you've got to stop thinking imperatively, stop thinking in terms of
是您必须停止命令式思考，停止在以下方面思考
loops,
循环
stop thinking in terms of using mutable state and variables to hold
停止思考使用可变状态和变量来保持
values. Think functionally
价值观。从函数上思考
remember the things that we've done in this course. Think,
记住我们在本课程中所做的事情。认为，
rather than using a loop, an explicit loop of
而不是使用循环，而是一个显式循环
using recursion, where you chain together a sequence of method calls, a
使用递归，将一系列方法调用链接在一起
sequence of functions
函数顺序
to provide repeated behavior.
提供重复的行为。
If you are going to use the forEach method think very carefully before you
如果要使用forEach方法，请在使用前仔细考虑
actually do it.
实际上做到了。
Is there a more functional way of replacing that forEach method?
有没有更实用的方法来代替forEach方法？
If you're just printing out values that's fine, but if you're trying to manipulate
如果您只是打印出值，那很好，但是如果您尝试操作
things
东西
within your forEach statement then you do probably need to
在forEach语句中，那么您可能确实需要
replace it
代替它
with more functional code. Streams
具有更多函数代码。流
can be infinite, but infinite streams don't need to go on forever.
可以是无限的，但无限的流不需要永远持续下去。
We saw that with using things like findFirst or findAny
我们看到使用findFirst或findAny之类的东西
you can terminate an infinite stream
您可以终止无限流
at a certain point when a particular criteria is met.
在满足特定条件的特定时间点。
The other thing, because we can
另一件事，因为我们可以
execute code in a stream in parallel
在流中并行执行代码
don't always think that the code is going to execute faster.
不要总是认为代码会更快地执行。
Yes, parallel enables you to do several things at the same time,
是的，并行使您可以同时执行多项操作，
but a parallel streams will always involve more work.
但是并行流始终会涉及更多工作。
Sometimes that will happen quicker than if you do sequentially.
有时，这比顺序执行的速度更快。
And that is the end of this three-week course.
至此，为期三周的课程结束了。
I hope you enjoyed everything that we've gone through, I hope that you find a lot of
希望您喜欢我们经历的一切，希望您发现很多
useful information here
有用的信息在这里
and it helps you to understand how to use Lambda expressions,
它可以帮助您了解如何使用Lambda表达式，
how to use streams and how to develop much
如何使用流以及如何发展
cleaner, much more elegant code using Java.
使用Java的代码更干净，更优雅。
Thank you very much
非常感谢你